[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "How many salmon are there?",
    "answer": "pála7",
    "number": "1",
    "a": "tsilkst",
    "b": "q̓em̓p",
    "c": "pála7",
    "d": "q̓em̓pálmen"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "How many salmon are there?",
    "answer": "q̓em̓p",
    "number": "10",
    "a": "án̓was",
    "b": "q̓em̓p",
    "c": "tsúlhaka7",
    "d": "pel7ú7pst"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "How many salmon are there?",
    "answer": "pel7ú7pst",
    "number": "8",
    "a": "pel7ú7pst",
    "b": "pála7",
    "c": "xw7útsin",
    "d": "tsúlhaka7"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "How many salmon are there?",
    "answer": "kalhás",
    "number": "3",
    "a": "t̓áq̓em̓kst",
    "b": "kalhás",
    "c": "án̓was",
    "d": "q̓em̓p"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "How many salmon are there?",
    "answer": "tsilkst",
    "number": "5",
    "a": "kalhás",
    "b": "pel7ú7pst",
    "c": "t̓áq̓em̓kst",
    "d": "tsilkst"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "question": "How many salmon are there?",
    "answer": "xw7útsin",
    "number": "4",
    "a": "q̓em̓pálmen",
    "b": "án̓was",
    "c": "xw7útsin",
    "d": "pála7"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "How many salmon are there?",
    "answer": "án̓was",
    "number": "2",
    "a": "án̓was",
    "b": "tsúlhaka7",
    "c": "q̓em̓p",
    "d": "kalhás"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "How many salmon are there?",
    "answer": "tsúlhaka7",
    "number": "7",
    "a": "tsilkst",
    "b": "pel7ú7pst",
    "c": "q̓em̓pálmen",
    "d": "tsúlhaka7"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "How many salmon are there?",
    "answer": "q̓em̓pálmen",
    "number": "9",
    "a": "pála7",
    "b": "án̓was",
    "c": "xw7útsin",
    "d": "q̓em̓pálmen"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "How many salmon are there?",
    "answer": "t̓áq̓em̓kst",
    "number": "6",
    "a": "tsúlhaka7",
    "b": "án̓was",
    "c": "pel7ú7pst",
    "d": "t̓áq̓em̓kst"
  }
]
